const store = {
    levels:[
        'easy',
        'medium',
        'high',
    ],
    words: {
        // A1 level
        easy:[
            {
                question: "school" ,
                answer: "школа",
            },
            {
                question: "children" ,
                answer: "дети",
            },
            {
                question: "market" ,
                answer: "рынок",
            },
            {
                question: "week" ,
                answer: "неделя",
            },
            {
                question: "party" ,
                answer: "праздник",
            },
            {
                question: "wallet" ,
                answer: "кошелёк",
            },
            {
                question: "price" ,
                answer: "цена",
            },
            {
                question: "road" ,
                answer: "дорога",
            },
            {
                question: "clean" ,
                answer: "чистый",
            },
            {
                question: "easy" ,
                answer: "легкий",
            },
        ],
        // B1 level
        medium:[
            {
                question: "delivery" ,
                answer: "доставка",
            },
            {
                question: "honest" ,
                answer: "честный",
            },
            {
                question: "knowledge" ,
                answer: "знания",
            },
            {
                question: "mirror" ,
                answer: "зеркало",
            },
            {
                question: "petrol" ,
                answer: "бензин",
            },
            {
                question: "fortune" ,
                answer: "судьба",
            },
            {
                question: "contest" ,
                answer: "соревнование",
            },
            {
                question: "background" ,
                answer: "фон",
            },
            {
                question: "ridiculous" ,
                answer: "нелепый",
            },
            {
                question: "at once" ,
                answer: "немедленно",
            },
        ],
        // B2 level
        high:[
            {
                question: "proof" ,
                answer: "доказательство",
            },
            {
                question: "success" ,
                answer: "успех",
            },
            {
                question: "alleviate" ,
                answer: "облегчать",
            },
            {
                question: "covert" ,
                answer: "убежище",
            },
            {
                question: "hasten" ,
                answer: "спешить",
            },
            {
                question: "noxious" ,
                answer: "вредный",
            },
            {
                question: "rescind" ,
                answer: "расторгать",
            },
            {
                question: "resolution" ,
                answer: "решительность",
            },
            {
                question: "temper" ,
                answer: "характер",
            },
            {
                question: "billow" ,
                answer: "лавина",
            },
            {
                question: "surgeon" ,
                answer: "хірург",
            },
        ]
    }
}